[
  {
    "question": "1 x 7",
    "options": ["6", "7", "8"],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 7",
    "options": ["12", "14", "16"],
    "correctAnswer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 7",
    "options": ["18", "21", "24"],
    "correctAnswer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 7",
    "options": ["24", "28", "32"],
    "correctAnswer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 7",
    "options": ["30", "35", "40"],
    "correctAnswer": "35"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 7",
    "options": ["36", "42", "48"],
    "correctAnswer": "42"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 7",
    "options": ["42", "49", "56"],
    "correctAnswer": "49"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 7",
    "options": ["48", "56", "64"],
    "correctAnswer": "56"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 7",
    "options": ["54", "63", "72"],
    "correctAnswer": "63"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 7",
    "options": ["60", "70", "80"],
    "correctAnswer": "70"
  }
]
